[Music]
[音乐]
this is Nick with logos by Nick comm and
我是尼克·康姆的标志尼克
in today's tutorial I'll be
在今天的教程中，我将
demonstrating how you can create these
演示如何创建这些
double exposure logos using Inkscape and
使用Inkscape和
if you'd like to learn more about how
如果您想了解更多有关如何
Inkscape works be sure to check out the
Inkscape作品请务必查看
Inkscape master class which is a
Inkscape主类，它是一个
collection of over 50 videos where I go
收集了50多个我去过的地方的视频
over all of the tools and features in
中的所有工具和功能
Inkscape and I explain what they are and
Inkscape和我解释了它们是什么
demonstrate how they work
演示它们的工作原理
I'll put a link in the description if
如果出现以下情况，我会在描述中添加链接
you want to check that out so I'm gonna
你想检查一下吗？所以我要
get started here in Inkscape the first
从这里开始使用Inkscape第一版
thing we want to do is just set up our
我们想要做的就是设置我们的
documents that we're all working with
我们都在处理的文件
this similar workflow I'm gonna come up
我将提出类似的工作流程
here where it says view and I want to
在这里，上面写着观点，我想要
make sure we have custom selected and
确保我们已经选择了定制选项，并且
then I'll zoom go to zoom zoom in at 1
然后我会放大到1点放大
to 1 and then I want to open up the
设置为1，然后我想打开
align and distribute menu with this
将菜单与此对齐并分发
button over here we're gonna want last
按钮在这里，我们想要最后一个
selected chosen from that drop-down and
从该下拉菜单中选择并选择
then I'll open up the Edit objects
然后，我将打开编辑对象
colors gradients and Stroke menu with
颜色渐变和描边菜单
this button right here so that we have
这个按钮就在这里，所以我们有
those two menus open now what we're
这两个菜单现在打开了我们是什么
gonna do is we're going to import some
我们要做的就是进口一些
graphics from from pixabay which is like
来自Pixabay的图形，就像
a free stock photo site with a double
一个免费的股票照片网站，有一个替身
exposure logo you're pretty much doing
你几乎是在做曝光标志
is you're taking two different objects
你拿的是两个不同的物体
and combining them together into one
并将它们结合在一起
object now let me show you what I mean
对象现在让我向你展示我的意思
here I'm gonna open up this website here
在这里我将在这里打开这个网站
I'll have a link to all of this
我会有这一切的链接
information in the description of the
描述中的信息
video I'm gonna take a combination of
视频中，我将拍摄一组
this like this silhouette of a skyline
这就像天际线的剪影
of trees here and combine it with one of
并将其与其中一种
these animals here for the thumbnail I
这些动物在这里的缩略图我
use the bear that's what I'll be using
用熊，这就是我要用的
in this tutorial so what I'm gonna do is
在本教程中，我要做的是
I'm going to download this click on free
我要下载这个点击免费
download I'm gonna choose the vector
下载我要选择向量
graphic the SVG download that let me
图形的SVG下载让我
minimize this and just click and drag
最小化这一点，只需点击并拖动
this into Inkscape there we go and I
这进入Inkscape，我们去那里和我
want to come over here and do the same
想来这里做同样的事情吗？
thing download this the SVG download
东西下载这是SVG下载
there we go
好了，我们走吧
click and drag that into Inkscape and
单击并将其拖到Inkscape中，然后
there we go now let me open up Inkscape
好了，现在让我打开Inkscape
again let me zoom out a little bit I'm
再说一次，让我放大一点，我是
gonna hold ctrl and roll down the mouse
按住Ctrl键并滚动鼠标
wheel a few times to zoom out I want to
滚轮几次缩小，我想
take this over here let me try
把这个拿过来，让我试试看
ungrouping this is seeing if I could
把这个拆开，看看我能不能
there we go just take this I'm gonna
好了，拿着这个，我要
work with this one with this one animal
用这只和这只动物一起工作
right here and I take the rest of these
就在这里，我把剩下的这些
and press Delete on the keyboard to get
并按键盘上的Delete键以获取
rid of them and what I'm gonna do is I'm
摆脱他们，我要做的就是
gonna take these objects and make them
我会把这些东西制作成
different colors and bring the opacity
不同的颜色和带来的不透明度
down so I can see them a little better
这样我就能更清楚地看到他们了
okay so I'm gonna start off with this
好的，我要从这个开始
object right here I'm gonna make this
对象就在这里，我要做这个
red bring me the opacity down roughly
红色使我的不透明度大致降低
and
和
and then I'll take the bear I'm gonna
然后我会带走那只熊，我会
make this blue and I'll bring the
把这个弄成蓝色，我会带上
opacity of that down roughly in half as
它的不透明度降低了大约一半
well and I'm gonna flick this
好的，我要把这个弹出来
horizontally actually enough where it
在水平方向上，实际上已经足够了
says up here flip selected objects
表示在此处翻转选定的对象
horizontally I'm gonna flip that over
水平方向，我要把它翻过来
there and I'm trying to position the
在那里，我正试图将
bear over the area of the trees where
在树木所在的区域承担责任
I'd like to combine it and I'm gonna
我想把它结合起来，我要
zoom in a little bit by holding ctrl and
通过按住Ctrl和
rolling up the mouse wheel if you want
如果需要，可以卷起鼠标滚轮
to move the page around you just press
要在页面周围移动，只需按
down the mouse-wheel and move the mouse
向下移动鼠标滚轮并移动鼠标
I'm just gonna hold ctrl and scale this
我只需要按住Ctrl键并进行缩放
up a little bit I want to grab a sample
再往上一点，我想拿个样本
basically what I'm going to do is I'm
基本上我要做的是
gonna take the bear and the trees and
带着熊和树
I'm gonna do a path intersection between
我要做一个小路的交叉口
the two of them and it's gonna create an
他们两个人，这将创造一个
object that combines the two of these
对象，该对象将这两者结合在一起
shapes right here but when I do that
形状就在这里，但当我这样做的时候
it's gonna cut out the tops of the trees
它会把树顶砍掉
here because that's extending further
在这里，因为它正在进一步延伸
than where the bear is but I want to
比熊在哪里更好，但我想
include those trees in this design so
在这个设计中包括那些树，所以
what I'm gonna do first is I'm gonna
我首先要做的是我要
grab it the Bezier pen which is over
拿起贝塞尔笔，它已经结束了
here you can just press B on the
在这里您只需按B键即可
keyboard it's a keyboard shortcut and
键盘这是一个键盘快捷键
I'm gonna manually create a shape going
我将手动创建一个形状
around the tops of these trees here and
围绕着这些树的顶端
I'm gonna unify it with the bear so let
我要把它和熊统一起来，所以让
me start out right over here I'm gonna
我从这里开始，我要
click to create a shape going around the
单击以创建一个环绕
outside around here let me zoom in a
在外面，让我放大一张
little bit so I can see this a little
一点，这样我就能看到这个了
better right over here there we go is
更好的是在这里，我们去那里是
zoom out bring it straight through the
缩小使其直接穿过
object and back to the starting point
对象并返回到起点。
like that now what I'm gonna do is go to
就像这样，现在我要做的是
the Select tool I'm gonna hold shift I'm
我要按住Shift键的选择工具
gonna click on the bear graphic with
我要用鼠标点击熊的图形
them both selected I'll go to path Union
他们两个都被选中了，我要去Path Union
and now I will hold shift and click on
现在我将按住Shift键并单击
the trees so that I have both of those
这些树，所以我两个都有
objects selected and I will go to path
选中的对象，我将转到路径
intersection you may have to give this a
交叉口，你可能需要给它一个
second to process because it's a pretty
第二个要处理，因为它是一个很漂亮的
uh it's a large photo here it looks like
这是一张很大的照片，看起来像
it didn't work for this one
对这一次不起作用
let me des elect it there might be this
让我来选吧，可能会有这个
actually might be a group of images so
实际上可能是一组图像，所以
let me try ungrouping this you see if
让我试着解开这个，你看看
that helps oh there we go
这很有帮助，哦，我们走吧
it was grouped that's why let me bring
它是分组的，这就是为什么我要带
the opacity down let me click off of the
向下的不透明度让我可以点击
graphic to deselect everything and start
取消选择所有内容并开始的图形
off with this again
又拿着这个走了
click on this hold shift click on this
点击这个按住Shift键点击这个
go to path intersection give it a second
走到小路交叉口给它一秒钟
and do its thing and there we go as you
做它该做的事，我们就像你一样
can see we have a combination of those
可以看到，我们拥有这些元素的组合
two objects there then let me bring the
那里有两个物体，然后让我把
opacity of this all the way up
一直到现在的不透明
let me make this black or dark gray and
让我把这个改成黑色或深灰色
and from here on out you can just go
从现在开始你就可以走了
ahead and add your test your text and
继续并添加您的测试文本和
whatever else you'd like to add and that
你还有什么要补充的吗？
should pretty much do it for this
应该为这件事做点什么
tutorial that's how you can go about
教程，这就是你可以如何去做
creating those double exposure style
创造那些双重曝光风格
logos using Inkscape if you have any
使用Inkscape的徽标（如果您有）
questions let me know and as always
问题让我知道，一如既往
thanks for watching
感谢收看
[Music]
[音乐]